[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This character, portrayed by Grant Mitchell, is Elaines father in Arsenic and Old Lace.", "correct_answer": "Reverend Harper", "incorrect_answers": ["Teddy Brewster", "Dr. Einstein", "Mr. Witherspoon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On which continent can you find the turltle-dove during most of the year?", "correct_answer": "Europe", "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "Antarctica", "South America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actor who lent his voice to Darth Vader also lent his voice to a character in The Lion King!", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Greek cheese is made of 70% ewes and 30% goats milk?", "correct_answer": "Feta", "incorrect_answers": ["Kasseri", "Metsovone", "Myzithra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The bread-slicing machine was first commercially used by the Chillicothe Baking Company of Chillicothe, Missouri.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This animals evolutionary lineage is the best documented and the most clearly understood.", "correct_answer": "Horse", "incorrect_answers": ["Human", "Dog", "Shark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the most expensive card in the game Magic: The Gathering?", "correct_answer": "Black Lotus", "incorrect_answers": ["Wildfire", "Mox Diamond", "Wrath of God"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Carter from Princess Protection Program work at the bait shop?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these years did the Italian national football team win the FIFA World Cup?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["1982", "2006", "1938"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the equation y = mx + b represent?", "correct_answer": "A line", "incorrect_answers": ["A hyperbola", "A parabola", "A circle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is the gestation period of a tiger?", "correct_answer": "16 weeks", "incorrect_answers": ["22 weeks", "10 weeks", "14 weeks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which lake is NOT one of the Great Lakes?", "correct_answer": "Great Salt Lake", "incorrect_answers": ["Lake Huron", "Lake Michigan", "Lake Ontario"]}]